SHIT, IT'S DARK IN HERE,
CAN'T SEE A DAMN THING,
WHERE THE HELL IS THAT BASTARD ANYWAY?
IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE DAY AND I STILL
HAVE TO FEEL MY WAY AROUND THIS HOVEL,
THIS BETTER BE WORTH IT.
Okay, if I remember correctly,
I'll find Dio over in that room.
Disgusting, this little lady
must be one of Dio's leftovers!
Damn bras just throw
themselves at the guy.
Like having their blood drank
is the latest bedroom craze.
The whole thing's nutty if you ask me?
Though girls do tend
to go for the bad boys.
But forget about that.
I've never seen so much gold in my life.
How'd he get all this?
It seems like this guy can have
and do just about anything.
Horse.
What is it?
It's...
Master... Dio.
Son of a bitch. What is this?
Just looking at him is enough
to send chills down my spine.
Keep it together, whole horse.
Don't let him spook you.
He's nothing to lose your cool over.
Yeah, he's not even that
much stronger than you.
I'll ask you again.
Did you want something, whole horns?
Uh, well, yes, actually.
There's something I
thought you ought to know.
I received intel that two
of the nine great gods,
Mariah and Alessi, have
been put out of commission.
And your point is?
Well, there's more.
We've got trouble coming.
Turns out Joestar and his gang
will arrive in Cairo tomorrow,
and only three of the nine gods are left.
It seems you've misunderstood my question.
I want to know what you're
going to do, whole horse.
You seem to have been
caught rather off guard.
I simply wish to know when you're
going to kill them, whole horse.
While it's true you've
pledged your allegiance to me,
you have yet to adequately
prove yourself in battle.
In this day and age, any
simpleton can deliver information.
Twice you've failed me, and
here you are crawling back.
You couldn't know this,
but my body once belonged to a man
by the name of Jonathan Joestar.
Jonathan was the grandfather
of Joseph Joestar.
Look closely.
Notice how the left finger heals
at a slower rate than the right.
The left side of this body is weak,
which proves that it doesn't
completely belong to me yet.
And that I am not yet immortal.
I am ill-equipped to fight a battle
with Joestar and his friends.
Now then, if there is nothing else, run
along and destroy my enemies on my behalf.
Failure will most assuredly
result in your untimely demise.
You're burking up the wrong tree, Haas.
As if threats are gonna make me
roll over and do whatever you want.
On your behalf, my ass?
I'm no fool.
I'm smart enough to throw
in with whoever's strongest.
Everything I've said has been lip service.
I'd never swear my loyalty to
you at the cost of my soul.
Rat bastard, you're not so tough, are you?
You're wide open.
Guess having another person's body
attached to your head has made you go soft.
This is perfect.
I don't have to fight
Joseph and the other three.
Not when I've got Dio in my crosshairs.
It'd be a hell of a lot easier to blow his
head to smithereens right here and now.
If I do, his treasures mine for the Taken.
This'll be a piece of cake.
He doesn't know Emperor's
aimed point blank at his skull.
I can finish him off and
he'll be none the wiser.
Just one pull of the trigger
and this nightmare will be over.
After all, Emperor was made
for close combat carnage.
I can do this.
Is there a problem?
You seem to be hesitating.
Eat lead, shitbag!
I'm about to splatter your brains
all over the floor, Mr. Dio!
Are you positive you want to
go through with shooting me?
He's gone!
Fascinating.
As you prepared to fire,
your breathing was relaxed.
You didn't even perspire.
You were composed.
Very impressive, whole horse.
This doesn't make a lick of sense.
I didn't even see him move.
There's no way in hell he
could have creeped up behind
me without breaking a single
one of those spider webs.
Fast or not,
he shouldn't have been able to sneak up
to my rear without me noticing something.
Was that the power of Dio's stand?
The power of the world,
ill-equipped? Yeah, right.
I finally understand, Master Dio.
I've got no choice but to pledge
my eternal loyalty to you.
You've got me beat.
I'll wake you in the morning.
In the end of the day of the world,
I'm afraid of the devil!
I'm afraid of the devil?
I'm afraid of him.
I'm afraid of him, I'm afraid of him.
Once you've got to play,
you'll now play the game?
This is when you're here!
To begin to fight for you.
Decide of the end!
Laugh, laugh, laugh!
At the last page of the last page.
The end of the world,
Ladies and gentlemen, we sincerely hope
you've enjoyed today's flight from Aswan.
We'll be arriving on schedule at
Cairo International Airport shortly.
Whoops, snooze you lose, buddy!
I hate to break it to you, cowboy,
but it looks like this is our cab now.
No hard feelings.
Huh?
Don't tell me you're going
to start crying like a baby!
Shit!
What the hell?!
Giza Pronto.
The Minoru House Hotel.
I'm gonna open up this
suitcase and let you out.
Unless you want some Card
pain, I suggest you keep calm.
We clear? Huh?
Did you, uh, say something just now, sir?
If I did, it sure the hell wasn't to you.
Now shut up and drive the cab!
Yes, sir.
Cut it out.
You know, if you weren't
making such a damn racket,
I wouldn't have had to hogtie you and put
you on the plane like a piece of luggage.
Don't be a baby, Mondatta.
Your brother's got another month in
the hospital thanks to that bomb,
so you and I are partners.
Now make sure those big ears are listening,
because here's what we're going to do.
We're going to use your
book of premonitions
and my assassin gun to stamp out Jotaro,
Joseph, and the rest of those SOBs.
Got that, Mondatta?
I get that we haven't
known each other long?
But from what I've gathered,
You're afraid of just about anyone
that's not your brother Zenyatta.
But don't you think this is the
perfect chance to avenge the guy?
You don't want to be a
yellow-bellied coward forever, right?
That's no good.
I'm out of options, too.
We've got no choice but to fight.
Time for us to get our revenge, Mondatta.
I'm gonna let you loose now,
but you have to swear to me you won't
carry on with all that infernal hollering,
okay?
See that, son?
I'm not so bad.
Now try and settle down, huh?
I don't need you getting sick on me.
Because believe it or not, I'm
on your side in this whole mess.
So don't you worry.
Just relax for now.
Huh?
Sir, why do you have
a puking kid? Shut up!
I see.
You got Moshe's sickness
from being on the plane.
Mondatta, let's be pals from here on.
How's that sound?
I'm Mondatta.
This is Whole Horse.
He's mean and I don't like him.
While Mondatta was sleeping, Whole Horse
tied him up and stuffed him in a trunk.
Mondatta was taken from
his brother Zenyatta.
He was sad.
But even though Mondatta
was scared out of his mind,
he wanted to avenge his brother.
So he decided to work up his courage
and become partners with Whole Horse.
Oh, come on.
You won't even get near me?
Well, I guess you're trying which
is all I can ask for at this point
And by the way,
I gotta know does your
stand really predict the
future or is that just
some cockamamie rumor?
If that was all just a tall tale,
then I brought you here for nothing.
I mean even with it your
brother got blown to high heaven
Which is it kid?
Are you a fraud?
How'd a new comic appear on a
blank page from out of nowhere?
While Mondatta and Whole Horse were
walking through the outskirts of Cairo,
they met a lady who was as
pretty as the day was long.
Then, Whole Horse jump-kicked
the lady in the neck! Hmm?
The pretty lady was so
overjoyed about the kick that,
out of the blue, she gave
Whole Horse her jewels!
Yahoo! We're rich!
What the hell is this crap?!
You must think I was born last night!
You call this a prediction, Mondatta?
There's just no way!
This crap has to be made up or something.
I'm telling the truth.
I stand, boss.
You just have to trust in its prophecies.
They're... they're...
they're 100!
They're 100 % right every time!
They're right 100 %?!
You trying to pull a wool over my eyes?!
There's no way some
lady's gonna give me her
jewels after jump kicking her in the neck!
You'd have to be off your rocker
to do something like that, hm?
Listen, Mondatta,
I'm proud to say that I'm a gentleman,
and a proper gentleman at that.
Because at that, I got
girls all over the world.
I might tell a white lie now and again,
but I'd never haul off and hit one.
I respect all the ladies, the beauties,
the plain ones, and even the ugly ones.
There's no way your prediction
will ever come to pass.
Come hell or high water, I
swear I will never hit a woman.
She could pay me every dime,
nickel, and quarter she had.
I still wouldn't put my hands on her.
It's 100 % true, yes.
See there?
Your fancy prediction was wrong.
Ah!
Who the hell are you?
What in the...
There was a scorpion in your shawl!
This thing's sting is a death sentence!
What?
You spotted that wretched creature before
it had a chance to crawl into my clothes.
If you hadn't killed it, she
would have been stung for sure.
You saved my life!
Oh, please, let me repay you.
Would my necklace be a sufficient reward?
It's yours.
Boy, this is my lucky day.
Mondana and I are practically invincible.
We'll be the unstoppable duo.
I don't think I'm going to
be able to help you, folks.
It's been my job to repair rooftops
in Cairo for around 40 years now.
And I can't say that I've
ever seen a place like this.
From the looks of the building's design,
the thing was built over
a hundred years ago,
give or take.
If I had to take a guess,
based on the picture,
I'd say you'd find it
somewhere south of here.
The buildings in Cairo get older and
older the farther south you travel.
Huh?
I'm sorry I don't have
more to go on, Sonny.
No, don't worry about it.
Sorry to bother.
All right, understood.
Thanks for the update.
I decided to make a call to Japan, and
my daughter's condition is much worse.
She's lost virtually all of her strength.
At best, she has three or four days left.
I can almost feel it.
It's like Dio's right on top of us.
I'd bet anything that he's
hiding somewhere close by.
But where could he be?
And how do we find him?
We should get moving.
We'll talk to everyone
here until we find him.
We've come this far.
We have to keep going.
Been a long time coming
but it's time for our
grand reunion I'm getting
sick of those faces.
I never thought they'd get so close
to Master Dio's mansion but they're
on the collision course for his
backyard and by the way listen Mondata.
We need to chat about your
latest prediction you sure it's
100% % foolproof it's more
than a little wacky they're not
dumb enough to fall for this
my premonition my premonitions
are always 100 percent accurate
is that what you're gonna say
well they are yes come on you
really expect me to buy this
load of baloney I think you've
lost your touch boy we found
them shouted whole horse Joseph
Jotaro Polnareff and Avdol
darn it whole horse fumed there
are hops giving a jump away.
for Master Dio's manner.
Those nosy buffoons will each
get a bullet between the eyes.
Whole Horse's mind was
full of violent thoughts.
You're gonna pay for my brother!
Mondatta was beside himself with anger,
but despite the pair
wanting immediate payback,
whole horse couldn't use his
gun, the Emperor, in the market.
Now, Whole Horse, Mondatta instructed,
stick your fingers all the
way up Polnareff's nose?
and then we'll win!
They're out cold from
losing all that blood.
Lucky you, Ho-Horse!
This is your chance to
finish them off for good!
Like hell I'm gonna buy that!
This is your big premonition?
Sticking my callous fingers at
Polnareff's booger-infested nose?
The hell do you take me for?
Well, speak, Mondatta!
The part about killing him sounds
good to me, but the rest of it?
You better not be planning
anything funny, boy.
I mean, come on!
Even if I was supposed to stick
my fingers at Polnareff's nose,
I'd have to somehow get
close enough to him to do it.
Instead of all that skullduggery?
I think we should go
with the direct approach.
and put a bullet in them with Emperor.
What do you say?
You're not gonna be able
to fire a bullet, yes.
Even though you tried firing your
stand, fate wouldn't let you, yes.
You have to trust me, yes.
I know from personal experience,
if you try to go against a comic,
you'll suffer the consequences.
It's fate, I tell you.
It's 100 % up to the whims
of fate, yes. Hang on.
Your brother followed the
comic and nearly died.
My brother was trying
to save himself but he
foolishly disguised himself
as Jotaro without thinking,
yes?
If he had trusted what he read
and not disguised himself,
then the real Jotaro would
have been blown up, yes?
The premonition itself was correct, yes?
Then what now?
Wait, where did Polnareff go?
Hey kid, Polnareff left the herd.
Find out where he went.
Shit! It can't be!
Don't you move!
Unless you'd like to be lanced.
But...
How the hell did you...?
Ombecile!
What exactly did you think you
were trying to pull just now?
If you know what's good for you,
keep your hands where I can see them!
I thought I noticed someone stalking
us like a desperate starving hyena and
wouldn't you know I was lucky enough to
stumble across our old friend whole horse.
It looks like you're still
trying to kill us which means you
haven't learned your lesson yet.
Say thanks for all the fun back in India.
You're very lucky Avdol survived our run-in
because if he hadn't you my friend would
Already be dead you here
alone whole horse no
way a coward like you
wouldn't come by himself!
I'm sure he's hiding out nearby
right well where's your partner crap
on the upside though He hasn't noticed
Mondata yet i still have a chance
Shit he's gonna see the book in his fingers
on your own you're not much of a threat
whole horse But I'm well aware that you
have a special talent for picking allies.
If you've found someone
to work with like before,
that could make you a dangerous obstacle.
Tell me, where did your partner go?
Out with it, where's the other stand user?
Your fingers.
Mondatta, hide your fingers!
If it gets wise to where
you are, it's all over!
You have to believe!
The reason you're in this situation
is because you tried using your gun!
Trust me, believe in fate!
If you believe in the power of fate,
our victory is guaranteed, yes?
I saw a hand go into the box,
which means my hunt was right.
What's the word, Polnareff?
Did you find the guy
that was following us?
Oh no, it's Avdor, and his
head is straight for us.
Believe, yes.
Put your faith in the book and stick
your fingers up Polnareff's nose, yes.
Are you serious?
Damn it!
I've got no choice!
Fine, I'll do it!
You, under the crate, show yourself!
Now, while he's looking the other way!
I know you're hiding under there!
What the hell?
Hell yeah!
Everyone bled so much,
they all passed out.
Lucky you, Ho Horse.
Now's your chance to finish them off.
So, what is this so-called
chance supposed to get here?
And what do I do till then?
Excuse me, Ho Horse, what
the hell are you doing?
You're not the only one who wants
to know the answer to that question.
I haven't the foggiest
idea where to go from here.
What am I supposed to do?
Hey, what's the matter, Polnareff?
He's not answering back.
Something's off. Shit! What now?
You threw on me like
white on rice! Damn it!
How the hell do I make the rest of
this stupid prediction come true?
This is crazy!
What am I supposed to do?
Do you believe it?
I believe it!
Hell Horse! Bingo! Copy!
I'm very lazy, but I
can't get the courage.
I'm a good man.
I'm 100 % of my manga.
This is how I can do it.
I can't believe it.
The prediction of the truth is
always true, it's a real lucky one.
The truth will make all
of it, if you do it.
All are fine.
You believe that!
Fire Force! Boring! Combine!
I believe it! Okay! You believe
it! Fire Force! Boring! Combine!
They've backed me into a corner.
I'm trying to give you a sign!
Look behind me.
Looks like there was a car
accident around the corner?
I made you boy some tea.
So have some lunch.
My fingers went up his nose.
And the prediction came true.
My premonitions are absolute!
It's fate. Yes.